http://secondcity.com/privacy

The Second City (TSC) has created this statement of our privacy policy in order to show our commitment to your privacy. The following describes our information gathering and sharing practices for this web site and its related digital marketing channels ("Web Site"). By visiting and using this Web Site, you agree that your use of the Web Site is governed by this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy also applies to any other features and online services provided by TSC that post or include a link to this Privacy Policy. Please note that if we provide access to other websites via links on this Web Site, those websites may have different privacy policies specific to those websites. We encourage you to read all third-party privacy policies because they will be different from this one, and may pose different privacy and security risks.
1. Information Collection
Via this Web Site or mobile applications, TSC may collect personal information including but not limited to your name, mobile or telephone number, email address, date of birth, Internet Protocol (IP), Media Access Control (MAC), International Mobile Equipment Identity (IMEI) addresses or similar identifiers, geographical location, and home or business mailing address. For the surveys provided as a part of our programs, we may collect certain additional non-personally identifiable information, such as preferences and answers to specific survey questions. In some cases, this type of non-personal information may be linked to personally identifiable information and in other cases it may not be linked back to individuals. For example, we may combine non-personal information about you and others who visit this Web Site, in which case, this aggregated information will not contain any information that can be linked directly back to you.
2. How TSC Collects Information
TSC may use any number of tools to collect information about you, your computer access points, and the web browser that you use to connect to this Web Site. For example, we use cookies, which are tiny text files placed on your computer's hard drive when you visit this Web Site. We may use cookies to personalize your interactions with this Web Site. You do not have to accept our cookies, you may set your browser to restrict their use, and you may delete them after we have placed them on your hard drive. If you do not accept or delete our cookies, some areas of this Web Site may take more time to work or may not work properly.
TSC may also collect information from your web browser each time you visit this Web Site. We may collect information about the pages that you visit and the time spent on each web page or area of the Web Site, the products and services that you click on, and other steps that you take while using this Web Site. This information may include the type of browser, the time that you opened this Web Site, and the referring web site's address.
Our Internet Service Providers (defined below) may use other standard web-based tools to analyze your use of this Web Site. The tools include web "beacons," "pixel tags," and "clear gifs." These tools help us ascertain information such as the effectiveness of our product and service marketing programs, allow us to tailor the services offered on or through this Web Site, and help promote the best use for the Web Site's content, and product and service offerings. Some of this information, including your IP, MAC, or IMEI addresses, may be stored on our Internet Service Provider's servers and logs for extended periods.
TSC may also request access to or otherwise receive information about your device location when you access the Web Site. Your location data may be based on your IP address. TSC uses location data in connection with providing our products and services to you, including by tailoring the products, services and other content presented to you, on the basis of your location.
3. Our Use and Disclosure of Your Personal Information
At times, TSC may use the services of third-party companies (who, in some cases, may be located outside the United States) to provide certain services to you, including, without limitation, website-hosting services, credit card processing, order processing and shipping services, and program participant surveys ("Internet Service Providers"). TSC may share your personal information with the Internet Service Providers as appropriate to conduct TSC business.
TSC may use your personal information to contact you via mail, e-mail, or electronic messaging in order to give you updates about TSC's special events, information regarding our products and services, or other promotions that may be of interest to you. We use return e-mail addresses to answer the e-mail we receive from you. TSC will not share your e-mail address with outside third parties for their direct marketing unless you give us permission to do so, but by registering with this Web Site, you authorize TSC to use your personal information for TSC's and its affiliates' marketing purposes.
In addition, we use your non-personal and personal information to tailor products and services specific to your needs; and we use such information to organize and manage our relationship with you, conduct business, improve our geolocation, provide program participant support, perform functions that are described to you at the time of collection, and enforce this Web Site's Terms of Use.
We may use non-personal aggregate information to improve this Web Site. For example, our Internet Service Providers may report to us that there were a particular number of visitors to a certain area of this Web Site, or that a certain number of program participants completed our registration forms in particular areas of our Web Site. TSC may use such information to analyze the effectiveness of our marketing models.
TSC may disclose your personal information as is necessary to: (a) comply with a subpoena or court order; (b) cooperate with law enforcement or other government agencies; (c) establish or exercise our legal rights; (d) protect the property or safety of our company and employees, contractors, vendors, suppliers, and customers; (e) defend against legal claims; (f) help with internal and external investigations; (g) detect, prevent, or otherwise address, fraud, security or technical issues; or (h) as otherwise required by law or permitted by law. We may disclose your information in connection with the sale or merger of our company or any transaction that involves the sale or assignment of some or all of our assets.
TSC and its service providers may store collected information for as long as needed for the purposes indicated in this Privacy Policy, which may be indefinitely.
4. Your Logon & Password
In order to maintain a secure environment, program participants may be required to use a login identification and password assigned to them by TSC to access certain areas of the Web Site. The use of this logon identification and password provides program participants access to the information and data within the Web Site to which they, and they alone, have been specifically authorized access.
TSC Web Site participants are also responsible for the control and use of assigned login identifications and passwords assigned to them. They should not be shared with anyone.
5. Data Storage and Security
TSC makes reasonable efforts to validate that our Internet Service Providers have implemented physical, electronic, and procedural security measures to assist with safeguarding your personal information, and to help protect against unauthorized access and disclosure. Only our authorized personnel and our Internet Service Providers who perform legitimate business functions for TSC are authorized to access your personal information. Notwithstanding our efforts, the Internet has inherent security risks. TSC cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, personal searches, and other communications will always remain secure. You should take care with regard to how you handle and disclose your personal information or any login or password that you are required to use to access services on this Web Site.
6. Interactive Areas
We may provide areas within the Web Site that allow users to post commentary and other materials. If we do, these interactive areas, such as discussion forums, are intended to enhance the user experience and build a community around TSC’s products and services. TSC shall not be liable for information posted in any such interactive areas of the Web Site. You acknowledge that, should you participate in such interactive areas, the information you voluntarily post about yourself and third parties in such areas might be accessed, collected and used by third parties other than TSC.
7. Children and Data Collection
TSC’s Web Site is for general audiences and is not intended for use by children. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen. If TSC or its Internet Service Providers become aware that a child under the age of thirteen has provided us with personal information without parental consent, TSC will delete that information from our databases. If you have questions about personal information related to a child, please email us at: legal@secondcity.com.
8. Your California Privacy Rights
Under California law, a California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship is entitled to request certain information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. However, under the law, a business is not required to provide such information if the business adopts and discloses (in its Privacy Policy) a policy of not disclosing a person’s personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the person first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure or the business gives the person a mechanism to opt out of having their personal information disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. We have chosen this alternative approach and provide California residents a mechanism to opt out of having their personal information disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and wish to opt-out of sharing your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes, please send us an e-mail request at: legal@secondcity.com and mark your request “California resident Opt Out”.
9. How You May Access and Change the Information that TSC Collects
The first time that you register with the Web Site, TSC will subscribe you to the TSC commercial e-mail or digital messaging distribution list and you will receive information about our products and services. Each commercial e-mail that we send to you will offer you the opportunity to opt-out of continuing to receive such messages. Please note that FTC e-mail compliance guidance allows us to send you transactional and relationship e-mails without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving those types of e-mails. For digital messages, your carrier's standard rates will apply and you my incur additional charges based on your carrier's data plan.
10. International Users
For those Web Site users located outside of the United States, we advise you that your personal information may, at times, be accessible to individuals who are located worldwide including in countries that do not provide the same level of data protection as in your country. By providing us with your personal information, you consent to our use of it in accordance with TSC's privacy policy, including the transfer of your personal information across international boundaries. The United States may not have data privacy laws that afford an equal level of protection for your personal information as the laws of your country.
11. General Information and Privacy Support Contact
TSC may update this privacy policy from time to time by posting a new version on the Web Site, and you should take the time to review it each time that you visit this Web Site. If you have questions or comments about our efforts to protect your personal privacy, or if you require additional information about TSC's privacy commitment, please contact us at: legal@secondcity.com.
026333.0009:20419549.2
Chicago Box Office
312-337-3992
Email Us
Drop Us A Note
Live Chat
Start A Conversation
Gift Cards
